Whoops.
Maybe I should've flown over the forest.
It's too late, though.
I guess I just have to keep going.
They say that beautiful flowers have thorns.
Occasionally, beautiful things will
bare their fangs when you touch them.
By the way, on another note,
who is this beauty blooming as
beautifully as the most colorful flowers?
That's right, it's me.
"The Girl as Pretty as a Flower"
What a magnificent field of flowers.
Oh?
Um, excuse me--
Oh, hello.
Are you the one taking
care of this flower field?
There's no one taking care of this flower field.
I'm just here because I like flowers.
I'm just playing with the flowers
while basking in the sun.
Then, these flowers are growing here naturally?
That's amazing...
Traveler, are you a witch?
I wonder if I might ask a favor of you.
I'll do what I can.
I'd like you to bring this bouquet
to the country you are about to enter.
I don't mind, but who should I give it to?
Anyone. What's important is that
someone thinks these flowers are beautiful.
In other words, you'd like me
to advertise this flower field?
You don't want to?
I'll do it happily.
Thank you, traveler.
Very well. I'll make sure
to give these to someone.
Take care!
Girl, stop!
"Girl"? Hmph.
Hey! Stop!
I told you to stop!
Do you have business with me?
Are you a traveler?
Can't you tell by looking?
What's with that bouquet of flowers?
It's nothing.
Show it to me!
Hey, wait!
You... Where did you get this?
Does it matter?
It has nothing to do with you.
Please return it.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'll take care of the rest. You go back.
Sir, this shawl... and these
flowers... They might be--
Go back!
Did you not hear me?
You should go rest.
Oh, please return the bouquet.
Here.
Thanks.
Sorry, Miss Witch.
Recently, his younger sister went missing,
and he's been like that ever since.
Please forgive him.
It doesn't bother me.
That's a lie, though.
By the way, sorry, but will you
let us dispose of those flowers?
They are not allowed into this country.
What do you mean?
Those flowers are poisonous.
Poisonous?
But I was fine...
They won't do anything to a witch,
but there's magic in them that will make
people who can't use magic go insane.
It makes people go insane?
Yes, people who are mesmerized by the flowers
are drawn to them like bees to honey
and led to where the flowers bloom,
becoming nutrients for them to feed off of.
That's why you must dispose of them?
Is something the matter?
No...
Sorry about this. You can go.
It was me!
Naw, you were just imagining it.
Flower field...
In my favorite book, The Adventures of Niké,
there is a story about a strange plant.
Normally, plants release magic
for us after absorbing sunlight.
But, through a sudden mutation,
it started sucking magic,
became sentient, and started acting violently.
That's what the story was about.
Could it be...?
The next day, before
I left for the next country,
I went to the flower field
I had visited the day before.
There was something I wanted to check.
Hello.
Oh, thanks for yesterday...
About your sister?
I finally found her...
...thanks to your bringing
her shawl and that bouquet.
I figured out that she was here...
I finally... finally found her...
You've become so pretty...
Trying to keep such
a wonderful place to yourself...
Come on, let's show this place
to everyone in the country, too.
I'm sure they'll like it.
Besides, I want to show you off now
that you've become as pretty as a flower.
Hey, that's fine, right?
I see, thanks.
You really are pretty...
"Bottled Happiness"
Hey...!
Oh, you came!
Hello.
Hello!
You're a real witch! That's amazing!
What're you doing in a place like this?
I'm a traveler.
So, I'm on a journey.
What about you?
I'm looking for happiness.
Happiness?
What's that?
It's a bottle where I'm gathering happiness.
You're gathering happiness?
I turn the moments people and
animals feel happiness into magic
and put them into this bottle!
So you can use magic, too?
Are you changing feelings into magic?
Yeah, you could say that.
Can I open it?
No, you can't.
If you open this here, then my
hard work will come to nothing.
These are precious treasures
I've been gathering for the girl I like.
Oh, are you mad?
No, I'm a little moved.
It reminded me of a book I read in the past.
A book?
Yes.
For the sake of his wife, who was sick
and couldn't leave the house,
a husband travels around the world,
recreating beautiful views with magic
so he could bring them home
and show them to his wife.
Oh? What happened?
I bet his wife was really happy!
I can't remember...
I'm sure she was healed and lived a long life!
Maybe that was it.
So, who's this girl you like?
She's a servant named Nino
who works at my house.
She always looks gloomy,
so I want to cheer her up.
That's why I'm bottling up happiness.
I see.
Feelings of plants?
Yeah!
I tried to see if I could
get happiness from them,
but it didn't really work.
You're lucky the plants didn't use you for food.
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, you can see it up ahead!
What a peaceful village.
Right?
Is that the village chief's house?
It's my house, too!
Oh?
You don't seem that interested, Miss Witch.
Would it be better for me to act surprised?
Wow, that's amazing! You're rich, aren't you?
Uh, right, never mind.
When will you give her that bottle?
I think I'll give it to her
after we finish lunch.
Oh, right! Why don't you come eat lunch with us?
The food Nino makes is really good!
Thank you for the invitation,
but I just ate breakfast.
Then, I'll make sure you get a smaller portion.
Are there any foods you don't like or can't eat?
I don't like mushrooms...
Got it. I'll make sure she doesn't put any in.
Please make sure it's a small portion.
Leave it to me.
The food'll definitely be really delicious--
made by Nino!
Anyway, make yourself at home.
Thanks.
H-Hello...
Hello.
Could you be from a land in the east?
Huh? U-Um...
Oh, you just seemed similar to someone I know.
You're right!
My dad found her in an eastern land.
Found...
So that's why you're here...?
Y-Yes...
The village chief is... very kind...
Where is the village chief?
He's working in his study...
Hey, hey, Nino! What's for lunch today?
T-Today, the village chief said
he wants... fish grilled with salt...
Can you make some for
Miss Witch over there, too?
It's fine, Miss Witch!
Thank you very much.
But please don't give me too much.
R-Right.
Oh, yeah, Nino!
I have a present for you after lunch.
F-For me?
Yeah! Look forward to it.
N-No, that's not necessary.
The village chief will be angry.
Don't worry about it! I'll explain to Dad.
No, but...
Then, this is an order from me:
Take the present, Nino.
How about that?
If it's an order...
Yeah!
Shall I help with something?
You can have a seat, Miss Witch.
We'll take care of the food.
Oh? It's unusual for us to have a guest.
Are you the village chief?
Indeed I am.
I am the traveling witch, Elaina.
Nice to meet you.
What a polite young lady.
Please make yourself at home.
Thanks for waiting!
S-Sorry to keep you waiting...
This is a small portion...?
Is something the matter?
No... Well, shall we eat...?
Let's eat!
Thank you for the food. It was very good.
O-Oh, thank you... very much...
I'll put the dishes away.
--I'll help, too--
--Oh, don't worry about it, Miss Witch.
You met Nino in a land in the east?
Yeah, I bought her.
Bought...?
She's a slave.
A few years ago, my wife left.
There was a period when we had
problems getting the housework done.
I found her in an eastern land when
I was there for work around that time.
She was expensive,
but she could do some housework,
and most of all, she is sure to
be a beauty when she grows up,
so I bought her without any hesitation.
As I thought, she's a great servant.
Does Emil know about this?
I told him,
but he doesn't care if the
other person is a slave or what.
Hey, Nino, where should I put the big plat--
What are you doing?!
You worthless piece of junk!
How long will it take before you
learn to do your job perfectly?!
Hurry up and clean it up!
--I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--Clean it up!
Stop it, Dad!
That was my fault just now.
--Nino didn't--
--You shut up!
Clean it up!
--Yes, sir...
--You don't need to clean it up.
Huh?
Next time, be careful not to drop it.
O-Oh, sorry about that.
For you to see something so disgraceful,
and then even fixing the china for us...
Come on, you thank her properly, too.
U-Um, I'm sorry...
At times like this, you should say "Thank you."
Thank you... very much...
You're welcome.
I could've done magic like that.
Oh my, I'm sorry.
Was my help unwelcome?
No. Thanks, Miss Witch.
You're very welcome.
But, I could've...
Speaking of which, Nino seems very
depressed right now, doesn't she?
Isn't this the perfect time
to give her present to her?
Miss Witch, you might be a genius!
Feel free to praise me more.
I said earlier that I had
a present for you, right?
Y-Yes.
Here, this is your present.
This is a bottle filled with happiness.
Happiness...?
It's filled with the happiness of
various people I found in various places.
The happiness of... various people...?
You can only see it once, so look carefully.
Come on, let's open it.
Ready, go!
These are pieces of happiness!
The outside world is
filled with all this happiness.
So don't always look so gloomy.
I'll make you happy.
Make me... happy...?
Come back and visit, okay?
When you come back,
Nino and I will make food that's
even more delicious for you! Right?
Yes, I'll come back and visit.
Bye.
Bye!
What lovely colors.
It was then that I remembered the
ending of the book I read in the past--
The beautiful scenes the husband brought home
ended up making his wife, who couldn't
go anywhere, even more depressed.
And then, his wife...
"Just because you are doing something
for someone else doesn't make it right."
It was a really preachy story.
Kindness and beauty can sometimes become cruel.
I don't know what happened to Nino after that.
No, I don't want to know...